

- 08005, Barcelona Spain
- +(34) 677 841 364
- khrystsina.kozak@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Dedicated Account Manager successful at handling numerous clients and issue resolution. Focused on attending various customer needs with achieving expectations. Expert salesperson and team player. Successful at increasing revenue with new accounts while maintaining relationships with existing ones.

SKILLS

- Strategic planning
- Cross-functional collaboration
- Customer orientation, "client-first" approach
- Issue resolution
- Goal-oriented
- · Self-motivated / Proactive
- Constantly eager to learn and improve

LANGUAGES

Russian: First Language English:	C1
Advanced Spanish:	C1
Advanced	()

Khrystsina Kozak

EXPERIENCE

May 2021 - November 2022

Publisher Account Manager, Exoclick | Barcelona, Spain

- Managed portfolio of key publishers, including DSPs and all demand sources to meet and exceed performance goals. Proactively resolving business and technical issues
- Managed the onboarding of new partners and thought of ways to grow them
- Pulled reports, analyzed data, reviewed sites and consulted partners based on findings
- Built and maintained productive relationships and administrative operations associated with partners (billing, deal set and troubleshooting)
- Projected planning and execution (Monday, HubSpot)
- Worked closely with technical team to resolve technical issues and provided support on S2S, oRTB, exads integration methods
- Prepared P&L reports and financial statements for review by management.
- Attended various networking events to identify sales opportunities and build relationships.

November 2016 - April 2021

Account Manager, Thevaluefactory SL | Barcelona, Spain

- Monetized databases (AU, UK, NZ, ES, BE, NL)
- Analyzed, reported and updated daily statistics
- · Negotiated contract conditions

February 2016 - October 2016

Account Manager ES/IT, Acai Performance | Barcelona, Spain

- · Negotiated with affiliates and acquired new partners
- Managed emailing campaigns (CPC, CPL, CPA)
- · Reported and actively solved any client-related queries
- · Managed and sending advertising campaigns
- · Established loyalty through email/CRM strategies
- Achieved monthly KPIs

September 2015 - February 2016

Account Manager AU, NZ, Natexo | Barcelona, Spain

- · Managing advertising campaigns, established network
- · Ensured daily monitoring of deliverability
- · Reported and updated results on the statistics platform

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2019

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT COURSE | Marketing

Online Training Center Netology-groups, Moscow, Russia, Russia

2015

Master of Science | Economics

Barcelona School of Management And ESCI-UPF, Barcelona, Spain, Spain

2014

Bachelor of Science | Economics

Belarusian National Technical University, Minsk, Belarus